[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Direct Superior Officers] [Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin]
Wow, "Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin."
The name itself is savage.
Hey! Line it up properly!
What will the colonel say if he sees it?
- Yes, okay. - Wow, this guy, seriously...
Never in my entire service
[Battalion Commander] have I seen congratulatory flowers.
[Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin]
- Chungseong! Love you! - Chungseong! Love you!
Yeah, love you too. Well done.
- Thank you, sir! - Yeah.
[Congratulations on your inauguration!]
[Congratulations]
[Congratulations, Lieutenant!]
How'd they know about the Second Company patrol's rotation
to get here to put all of this up?
The commander's popularity's no joke.
Yeah, he even missed the inauguration ceremony.
This is what his message read.
Thank you to all of you who congratulated me on my inauguration.
However, I have to respectfully turn down the wreaths and flowers.
If you would really like to, please send rice instead.
This way we can share it with people in need.
Goodness.
I'm not certain, but I've heard this guy's a kid.
[From the 6th Corps Commander...] Wow, even the corps commander sent stuff.
[Song Jae Gwang] Oh, this guy's connections...
He's really different from you.
I never told you this, but...
I've got some serious connections, too.
Oh, really?
Don't say internet connection or something like that.
Huh?
- Huh? - What?
What?
Hey, you joke too much!
Ah, this guy, seriously.
If I make battalion commander in the future, I'll send you one.
Oh my, thank you for even saying that.
But who knows if that day will ever come.
Hey, of course it will!
Oi, No Hee Jeong, did you order the guys to clean?
Yes, I did.
- Choi Il Gu. - Yes, sir?
Did you update the situation board?
Uh, no... Why would I...
Hey, Choi Il Gu.
- Yes, sir, I'm Choi... - Enough.
You're an officer now. Start acting like one.
Okay, I will, sir.
What the hell is this?
This just appeared now, I don't...
For God's sake.
Chungseong! Love you!
Love you too! Where's the company commander?
He should be here soon.
Are you all waiting?
That's right, he...
told us all to wait in the barracks.
Oh, I see, well done.
One of you is missing?
The platoon leader said
he'd go ahead to receive the battalion commander.
[Devotion to the Nation]
Chungseong! Love you!
Chungseong! Love you! You're doing great.
Have a good day, sir!
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin!
Always combat-ready and prepared to respond to enemy prov...
Is that too much?
Oh, he's going to go places.
Yeah, looks like he'll make captain in no time.
So many bats in this unit.
Corporal No Bat...
- What? - Never mind.
Okay, back to it then.
Yes, sir.
- You just flipped me off, didn't you? - Sorry? No!
Yeah, you did.
No, I didn't, I would never!
You did so!
No, sir, really, my glasses were slipping.
I just used my index finger.
If you get caught flipping someone off, you have to hang upside down and work.
You have to eat upside down, too.
And when you're sleeping.
Corporal No Bat, understood, sir...
Yoon Mo, pass me the scissors. Let's cut this bat off, come on!
- Hey, Il Gu, call the medic! - No, I'm serious!
- Ah, yes, okay! - It was an accident!
I was just pushing them up, I swear!
- Breathe, breathe! - No, no!
It'll grow back, don't worry.
It's boiling, right?
When will the damn military get an air conditioner?
What is this, a sci-fi movie?
That'll never freaking happen.
Still, getting to skip the inauguration was pretty sweet.
I'm dying just thinking about standing around in that heat.
I've heard he's pretty young. Maybe that's why he's a bit different.
"Different," my ass.
You know why he skipped inauguration?
No, why did he?
The last battalion commander got ousted that way.
So would you do it if you were him?
- Ah. - Jeon Se Gye!
These folks are busy, but give them an autograph.
You exploited Jeon Se Gye's sick mother and used an officer for personal gain.
Can you still call yourself an officer?
Is this what the military is?
Hey, Jeon Sekai.
Private Jeon Sekai!
Do you know what happened to him?
I also heard he was transferred somewhere, but I don't really know the details.
I heard he went to the hospital to see his mom.
Damn, he really put on a big show to get a lighter punishment.
That blue blood was off from the get-go.
Se Gye, how's your mother doing?
When I saw her during leave, she was doing much better.
I spent most of my time there.
The hospital must've been chaos, huh?
A little.
I asked the nurses to take care of my mom.
I took some pictures and signed some autographs, too.
Hm, nothing else?
They asked to send letters, so I gave them your names.
Honestly, how could I not love you?
Se Gye.
Did you mention I'm getting discharged soon?
I even told them your discharge date!
- Yes! - Nice!
Hey, Sergeant Choi, don't you have a girlfriend?
Man, you're doing too much!
Byeong Nam, don't forget Su Ah promised she'd arrange
a group blind date for us when we're on leave!
Don't worry about that, okay?
My Su Ah is a beauty, remember?
Pretty girls hang with pretty girls, birds of a feather, right?
That's why beauty is pain!
What are you on about...
Chungseong! Love you!
And with the rice out front,
he said to gather it and donate it around the area,
so once you're done, just stack them neatly to one side, okay?
- Yes, sir. Go check. - Okay.
The battalion commander is here.
[Congratulations on your inauguration!]
[EP02. Battalion Commander Byeon Hyeok Jin] Attention!
Chungseong!
Chungseong.
- At ease. - At ease.
Second Company Commander, Cho Baek Ho!
Great, nice to meet you.
First Sergeant, Park Jae Su!
- First Sergeant, let's get along well. - Yes?
Yes, sir.
Assistant Platoon Leader, Sergeant Im Seong Min!
Yes, nice to meet you.
Senior Squad Leader, Staff Sergeant Choi Il Gu!
I love your energy.
Thank you, sir!
Platoon Leader, First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin!
- First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin. - Yes, sir!
Look out for me, yeah?
I'll look out for you, sir!
Great.
Hey, he just went into the admin office!
- You're all ready, right? - Yes, sir!
Okay, your nails are all cut?
- Yes, they're cut! - Yes, sir!
Okay.
I saw him at the main entrance yesterday,
and it was only for a second.
But he was super intense.
- Really? - Yeah.
We're screwed.
- Hey, Bit Na Ri. - Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri!
Don't mess up.
- Understood, sir! - Okay.
- Hey, new recruit. - Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
- You have to do well. - I will, sir!
Well, you'll do fine regardless.
Thank you.
Right, it's great to meet you all.
I am Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin.
"Chungseong! Love you" is the Second Company's motto, right?
Yes, that's correct!
Right, "Love you."
Well, it's good.
- Let's get along well! - Yes, sir!
I'd like to introduce myself to all the Second Company personnel, but...
Ah, yes, I'll...
You can do it h-here!
- Thanks. - Corporal No Hee Jeong, thank you!
Chungseong! Love you.
I'm Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin, the newly appointed Battalion Commander.
I'll keep this brief.
Bullshit. I'll call Dong Woo "hyung" if this is short.
Oh, you promise?
In the military,
your time spent here is in no way a waste,
nor is it a pause in your lives.
To help you all change and grow,
this unit will continue to transform alongside you
to stoke that growth.
That's all.
"That's all?"
Can it really be that short?
What, why?
Didn't you say you'd call me "hyung?"
Are you crazy? You wanna die?
- Wow! - Smooth.
Did he really finish?
In my entire military career,
I've never heard an officer make a speech that short.
- Do I just press this? - Oh, I'll...
No, no, it's fine.
Okay, sir...
- Let's head to the barracks. - Yes, sir.
I'll...
Allow me to show you.
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin.
First Lieutenant Oh Seok Jin!
No need to swarm us.
The company commander and I will go by ourselves.
I was just worried the commander was tired...
Yes, of course.
- Okay, back to it. - Yes, sir.
By the way.
Doesn't the new battalion commander seem pretty awesome?
"In the military,
your time spent here is in no way a waste nor is it a pause in your lives."
When he was making that speech,
he became my new role model.
You have so many role models. It must be nice.
Every damn person he sees becomes his "role model".
But when I met you, it wasn't...
What did you just say?
- Nothing... - Hand me those scissors from earlier.
- Yes, sir. - Come over here a second.
I've got somewhere to be, so I'll just...
Have a good day!
He got good at reading the room, huh?
Seems like it, sir.
Unit, attention!
Chungseong! Love you!
- At ease. - At ease.
Are you the newest recruit of the Second Company?
Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
Yes, that's correct!
Well...
I'm the greenest guy here now.
Let's get along well!
Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
I'll work hard!
Great, you're lively.
Corporal Park Min Seok.
Corporal Park Min Seok!
Corporal Park Min Seok! Thank you!
Nice to meet you.
Ah, yes, nice to meet you, thank you!
Ever since I heard Major General Park Chun Gyu's speech when I was a cadet,
his words have really stayed with me.
I have no doubt that under such a fine father,
you'll serve as a fine soldier yourself.
Yes, sir, I'll work hard!
Great.
Let's work well together, everyone!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
That's it.
Unit, attention!
Chungseong! Love you!
Chungseong! Love you.
He's way nicer than I thought?
That's the first time I've seen someone like that.
Yeah, he's not giving soldier energy.
More like a team leader at a corporate company.
He's actually so cool.
It must be nice. Park Min Seok.
Oh, Bbak Min Seok!
Having a military dad really is the ultimate military cheat code.
No way.
What do you mean "no way," dude?
You're definitely scoring a leave pass before you discharge.
No, trust me, that's definitely not happening.
That's exactly how the army works, dude.
Full of energy, Second Company.
Thank you.
Effective tomorrow, this battalion's going to have some big changes.
I'll be relying on you a lot, Commander Cho.
Understood, sir.
Wait, no.
I should be the one making a good impression on you, Commander Cho.
If I don't want to get booted.
Ah, that's, I...
I'm joking.
Is that the next one?
Yes, that's right.
Hey, today's going to be brutal, so everyone stay safe out there.
Hey, pick up the damn pace! Day's gonna be over by the time you get here!
Yes, okay, sir!
Quickly, run!
Hey! Watch the sickles!
Hey, hurry up, quickly!
Final years, not running?
I learned this pace back when you were a final year, Sergeant Choi!
Cut us some slack!
Shut up and hurry!
Chungseong! Love you!
What sort of salute is that?
We're going to up and do some weeding.
You boys holding sickles, stop messing around before you split someone's skull open.
I'll explain more when we're there, come on.
- Understood, sir! - Understood, sir!
- Let's go up. - Yes, okay!
Wow, the weeds have gotten pretty thick.
Fertile soil there.
Nearing discharge means we won't have to climb up here much more.
The clouds are pretty!
- Hey, everyone listen up. - Listening.
We're gonna do some weeding now.
First, clear out all of this side.
Then we move over there.
But if you look closely,
that's the Command Sergeant Major's crop patch he manages.
Only pull the weeds around it out.
Mess anything up and you're going straight to the brig. I'm serious.
You get what I'm saying?
- Yes, understood. - Yes, understood.
Okay, also...
I hate looking at this thing, who's taking the weed-whacker?
"Weed-whacker?"
Is something wrong?
Yeah, there is.
Back in the day, it wasn't just used for weeds.
Those were the fucking savage ages...
Well, anyway.
Weed-whacker volunteers, hands up!
I don't want to.
Look, it sucks, but someone has to do it.
Shut your mouth, for God's...
Hey, look here, I'll sweet-talk them.
Try it.
Uh... You.
Look, anyone below Ji Jeong Min, gather around.
Pass me that sickle.
- Corporal Park Min Seok. - Okay.
You guys think it'll be easier swinging this around?
No way. Look at it, yeah?
The blade's not even sharp. What can you even do?
Scratch your back with it?
Honestly, pulling them out by hand would be faster.
- Bullshit. - For God's sake, what are you snickering at?
You think doing it by hand will be easy?
No way, try taking your gloves off later.
Your fingers will all be green.
You go on leave with hands like that and your mom will cry.
You guys want to be terrible sons, huh?
What's with this punk?
Sorry, sir!
But!
Look at this weed-whacker.
Just strap the engine on your back and walk straight.
Fucking cake walk, right?
Bullshit.
Right, weed-whacker volunteers, hands up!
Ah, these bastards.
I really wasn't going to say this, but...
You all know Sergeant Shim Jin Woo, right?
- You know how to use a saw? - Yes, before the military, my nickname was...
That guy used the weed-whacker so well that he made the First Sergeant's day.
He got excused from tactical training to do it!
I'm telling you, it's freaking gold!
Of course, straight lies.
Right, I'm really asking for the last time.
Weed-whacker volunteers, hands up!
Even a stray dog knows weed-whackers are brutal.
Who the hell would do it?
It's so freaking hot, please just do rock-paper-scissors.
I'll start with you, Choi Byeong Nam, I swear.
- Oh please, stop that. - Please, stop that.
- Private Moon Bit Na Ri! - Ah, Jesus!
I'll do it!
Uh, anyone else? Nobody?
There must be...
There has to be, there must be!
Private Moon Bit Na Ri!
I've actually been waiting to do this.
Really?
Fine, okay, you do it.
Thank you!
- Ah... - I've got a bad feeling...
He'll slice the whole unit up instead of the weeds.
Hey, will you be okay?
- I will! - Be careful.
Shouldn't somebody stop him?
Sergeant Choi, look, I have goosebumps!
He cranked it up on the first pull...
Is he a weed-whacking prodigy chosen by the Gods?
There's no way it can start from the first pull!
When it doesn't start up the first time in the blazing heat,
it makes you want to smash the damn thing!
You look so cool!
Na Ri, you're awesome!
- Yeah, so cool! - You're awesome!
You look like Firebat!
Hey, everyone back up!
Hey, Bit Na Ri, go all the way to the end.
- Yes, sir! - Okay.
- Be careful, Na Ri! - Careful!
Well done!
Oh my God!
I guess every dog has its day!
He's giving Sergeant Shim a run for his money, no?
Wow, Na Ri!
Na Ri!
You're our hope!
Wipe it clean!
Bit Na Ri, you saved us!
Bit Na Ri, nice!
Bit Na Ri, fighting!
Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri! Thank you!
We're being swarmed from all sides by the enemy!
Request an artillery strike right now!
Coordinates are 322, 542! 322, 542!
Requesting immediate fire!
Enemies are assembling on the north ridge!
Do you copy? Do you copy?
Ah, for God's sake!
We've lost communications!
Where the hell is Moon Bit Na Ri?
We're all gonna die out here!
If Moon Bit Na Ri were here...
Min Seok!
Hold on a bit longer!
Bit Na Ri is going to come!
Min Seok, stay with us!
We're done for.
This is the end.
Sergeant Kim Sang Hun.
I will always cherish the memories of you as our squad leader!
Stay with us!
Park Min Seok!
I'll be with you until the end!
- Min Seok! - Love you!
- Min Seok! - Min Seok!
Oh, over there!
It's Moon Bit Na Ri!
- Moon Bit Na Ri has come! - Moon Bit Na Ri is here!
We're saved!
Oh, nice job, Bit Na Ri!
Thank you!
- You're built for crew-served weapons! - Yes, sir!
Wow, well done, Bit Na Ri.
Go over there first and get started.
Yes, sir!
Let's do this quickly!
Yes, got it!
If you finish fast, Kim Sang Hun will buy PX snacks!
Oh, really?
Okay, sure, I will.
Hey, Bit Na Ri, look!
Okay!
No, look, look!
I'm looking.
No, I said look!
You look nice, sir!
You dumb-ass, look where you're cutting!
Huh? Oh! No!
We're fucked.
Isn't this a ticket to the brig?
For God's sake... Is he crazy?
What's his problem?
At this point, wouldn't green tape be better?
- Yeah, it wouldn't be too obvious. - Right?
I heard tonight's dinner is stir-fried pork...
Did you do this on purpose to get lettuce wraps?
- I'm sorry! - Be quiet and get on with it.
Yes, understood, I'm sorry!
But, what's the point of doing all this weed-whacking
when we'll have to do it all again tomorrow?
Wouldn't it be better to just buy weed-killer and sprinkle it all over?
- Min Seok. - Corporal Park Min Seok.
We're cheaper.
Say that again, sorry?
I said we're cheaper than weed killer.
For the price of one bottle, they could probably hire ten more of us.
How much do you make, Min Seok?
Around 97,000 won a month?
Excluding weekends...
That's a daily rate of 4000 won a month.
If you divide that by an 8-hour shift...
Damn, it's 500 won an hour.
No overtime pay either.
Clocking out equals deserting.
Still, at least we get room and board.
Damn, 500 won...
So, if we add all our wages up together,
our hourly wage is...
[4,000 won] Min Seok.
Stop, I'm having an existential crisis.
Yeah, sorry.
Hey, hey!
Dude, why are you putting it right against the ruler like that?
The line will sever if you do it like this!
This is basic common sense.
Do I really need to walk you through this?
Chungseong! Corporal Ji Jeong Min here on official business.
We've come to pick up supplies.
- Like what? - Work gloves.
- Work gloves? - Yes.
Here, go.
There, off you go.
But, what are you doing?
What does it look like? Just wasting my time.
Hey, "wasting time" is what we're doing out there today, covered in dust.
Pulling out weeds is pointless.
Sitting under a fan with scissors? That's luxury.
Right.
Wow, the attitudes of these guys...
This is freaking difficult!
You came here to protect the country, but you spend all day cutting paper.
Admin guys really have it easy.
Did you just say "easy?"
Real talk, during morning roll call when it's boiling or freezing outside,
all you have to do is stay inside and sort documents!
Right, and you don't even have to stand night watch!
I'm seriously so envious.
Where the hell does this look "easy?"
Instead of roll call,
we get crushed under mountains of paper and get shredded by paper cuts.
It hurts, it freaking hurts, do you know the pain?
If your body's exhausted, at least you can sleep!
I hear auditory hallucinations of Corporal No in my dreams
screaming at me because one Excel cell didn't align!
- That's not a dream. - Wait, what?
You're getting chewed out today, too.
Hey, at least you're nice and cool in summer and warm during winter!
Wow, these guys really know nothing.
Weather's not what's important.
It's the officers' body temperatures that matter!
First Sergeant, Platoon Leader, Assistant Platoon Leader!
Look, if even one bubble gets under the contact paper?
Your entire soul will be ripped apart.
[Jeon]
What the hell is this?
It's all crooked!
You must be all twisted and crooked, too.
Your mind must be straight if you want your lines straight, kid!
Sorry, I'll do it again!
Hey, are you doing what I told you?
Yes, I-I-I'm doing it!
The guard duty rota's almost out...
Take your time, go on.
Though, guard duty reporting is around the corner.
I-I-I'll get it done right away!
You could've finished it in the time you were talking!
Are you ignoring me?
Hey, we really are in the advanced barracks now, huh?
You said not to talk, so...
We didn't say don't talk.
We said that in the time you were talking,
you could've finished by now, you idiot! Hurry up!
You wanna go train instead?
You're sitting under a fan, playing with scissors!
Hurry the hell up, bastard, hurry!
Yes, sorry, I'll hurry, sir.
Your answers are half-assed!
- And your work is half-assed, huh? - No, it's...
No, it's going to go wrong if you do that...
Are you out of your mind, hey, Sung Yoon Mo!
- Sorry? - You can't even type right?
Sorry, sir, sorry.
- No Hee Jeong! - Sorry, sir!
- Corporal No Hee Jeong! - Hey, Sung Yoon Mo!
Corporal Sung Yoon Mo!
- Sung Yoon Mo! - No Hee Jung!
- Corporal No Hee Jeong! - Sung Yoon Mo!
- Corporal Sung Yoon Mo! - No Hee Jeong!
No, sir, if you push me like that, it'll...
- Sun Yoon Mo! - No Hee Jeong!
- Corporal Sung Yoon Mo! - No Hee Jeong!
- I'm sorry! - I'm sorry!
Not this, this!
When the body has it easy, the mind is ripped apart.
The mood swings and fickleness of these officers
tear people to shreds.
Making me start from goddamn scratch because one Excel cell doesn't line up!
Whirr-clack, whirr-clack.
Whirr-clack, whirr-clack!
Do you know the horror of hearing those printers
spitting out paper all night like they're screaming?
I know this for a fact.
Whatever, it's still a luxury.
Okay, Yoon Mo, you've worked hard.
Corporal No, you've worked hard too.
Yeah, sure, we've got loads of things to do, so just go.
Yes, sir, hang in there.
Chungseong! Love you.
Eat this whilst you're at it.
We'll be off.
Yoon Mo.
Corporal Sung Yoon Mo.
Well done.
Thank you.
What did I say the number one rule of being an admin clerk was?
"You must always look exhausted in front of others."
Exactly, and number two?
"Don't forget rule one."
Exactly.
The second any of them hear that we have it easy,
we'll get dragged out for training.
You have to always be locked in with your method acting. Got it?
Yes, understood.
- Great. - So, then...
To numb the pain for a moment, you wanna play Pikachu Volleyball?
This bastard wants to play games during work hours...
Of course!
I'll be the right side.
But you were right side last time, too.
And so?
Nothing, never mind.
- I'm taking this, okay? - Sorry?
He gave it to me.
Hurry up!
Bastard.
Hey, you prepped everything, right?
- Yes, sir! - Great, well done, guys.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
Hey, what are you doing bringing that out now? You should've already prepped it!
- Sorry, sir. - For goodness sake.
[Lieutenant Colonel Byeon Hyeok Jin, Commanding Officer, 7th Battalion]
Okay, got it.
Right, get ready!
The Battalion Commander is here!
Unit, attention!
[Battalion Commander! Congratulations on Your Inauguration!]
Salute to the Battalion Commander!
- Chungseong! - Chungseong!
Chungseong!
Chungseong.
Now.
- At ease. - At ease.
Wow, you guys prepared so much.
It's just me, you didn't have to!
The atmosphere of this unit is amazing! Thank you!
Operations Officer, Major Kim Gwang Tae!
All the battalion officers prepared this to welcome our new commander
who chose to forgo his inauguration ceremony!
Thank you.
I heard you're the youngest lieutenant colonel.
You're really amazing!
I read your interview in Defense Daily and they called you
"the rising star of the next generation of commanders."
I'll learn a lot from you!
Please, I'm the one who should work hard.
A round of applause for the Battalion Commander!
Yes, thank you. Hold on, wait, wait!
But, if all the battalion officers are here,
then who's keeping an eye on things?
We left essential personnel behind.
- "Essential personnel?" - Ah, yes.
There are admin staff and operations specialists
from each company monitoring things in the control center.
The "essential personnel..."
So, then, are there "non-essential personnel" in our unit?
Sorry?
Ah, that's...
We heard you were coming, so we all came here to congratulate you.
We've always done it this way.
Ah, "always done it".
It's always been like this?
- Sorry? - It's a tradition
for battalion officers to leave their posts unattended and come gather like this?
Lieutenant Colonel, I understand what you're saying,
but today's your welcome ceremony, and for our officers' morale, well...
"Officers' morale?"
Then, what about the soldiers' morale?
All the food and the banners prepared here today,
did you all personally prepare them?
You didn't order the soldiers to do it?
Is it any wonder that soldiers joke that
their real enemies are their own officers?
I think that soldiers' morale comes from trust.
Trusting the commanding officers in this room.
Trusting your peers beside you, and through that, trusting the organization.
If you break that trust,
the strength of the army crumbles, too.
A military where we can trust each other, thus a military everyone can trust.
Whilst I am here, I am going to make all of these changes.
To the military, to all of you, everything.
Do you understand?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
I'll accept the gesture from the officers who prepared this today.
The soldiers diligently prepared this,
so please enjoy!
- Hyeon Uk. - Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
- Was today your first night watch? - Yes, that's correct.
- Oh, come, sit down! - Okay.
So, the night watch, well...
I did it at training camp, so it's nothing special.
So just, I guess, how to be a bit careful?
- I'll tell you a few ways. - Okay, great.
First, if a senior wakes you up,
get up immediately, change, and take over right away.
Anyone on guard duty needs to be woken up 30 minutes early though.
Oh, and when you wake them up,
never touch the senior like this, never, okay?
Just go up to their side quietly,
"Corporal Park Min Seok, it's time for guard duty.
You have to wake up." Wake them like this, okay?
- Yes, got it. - If you're too loud,
you'll wake everyone else, and they'll curse you out so bad.
- You've got to be really careful, okay? - Yes, understood.
Oh, and if you're checking the room temperature and it's too hot,
you can sprinkle some water on the floor like this.
But again, be super careful not to splash any on their boots, yeah?
Yes, got it.
What else...
Oh, you'll sometimes come across people who snore really loudly.
In that case, don't wake them up,
but there's this pillow, right?
You can just nudge it, gently though.
- That should work. - Okay, got it.
Yeah, that's pretty much it? Not hard, right?
- No, sir, it isn't. - Yeah.
If you get into a bind,
or something goes wrong, go straight to admin...
No, just wake me, actually.
- I couldn't. - No, it's all good, you can!
Got it?
- Okay, I understand. - Cool.
I mean, you always do well, so.
- Thank you. - You wrote it all down?
Yes.
- Hello, sir! - Yeah.
You trained him well, right?
Yes, sir, I did.
- Learned a lot? - Yes, sir, I did.
Wow, I remember Park Min Seok's first night watch.
It's hard to forget.
Oh? What happened?
Hey, Moon Bit Na Ri, be quiet.
Come on, what's the big deal, dude?
Back then...
What is it again?
[Temperature Reading] [Barracks No.1]
Crap...
Do I have to report this?
Damn it, I've just got to do it.
Where are you going, punk?
Oh, Corporal Choi Il Gu.
Have you checked the temperature and everything?
Yes, I've done the temperature readings, but...
But what? Is there something unusual?
There's an empty cot.
What?
I didn't see anyone go, though?
- What barrack? - Barrack one, sir.
- Barrack one? - Yes.
Wait, is that not your cot?
Right, yes, that's right!
Wow, I was worried.
Wow, it was so fucking funny.
I remember.
They're all old stories now, no?
Hey, Moon Bit Na Ri, mind your face.
Sorry, sir.
You're smiling?
I'll give you something to smile about!
- You're smiling, huh? - I'm not!
Hey, what are you doing!
- Did you really learn anything? - Yes, I did, sir!
- Okay. - Get over here. Hyeon Uk, grab him!
Private Kim Hyeon Uk! Okay...
- Guys, calm down. - Take care, sir. Goodbye!
Grab him now, quickly, quickly!
- Hey. - Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
- Get ready. - Okay, sir.
Oh, I'm gonna die.
Hey, Sang Hun, what time is it?
Right now it's 3:45 a.m.
Oh?
Wait...
Why haven't those punks come to swap guard posts?
I'll go check the night watch now.
[Guard Post Hotline]
Go out and check!
Yes, sir!
This is communications security. Okay.
Yeah, I'm already looking into it, okay.
I'll sort it out right now and send them. Hang in there a bit longer.
Yeah, sorry.
These goddamn slackers, 15 minutes late...
Fucking hell, these bastards.
Hey, which night watch bastard...
Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
I'm sorry!
Hey, where's his mentor?
Corporal Yoon Joon Young.
I'm sorry, I should've woken you!
Go wake all the squad leaders.
- Could you repeat that, sir? - You heard me.
Go wake the squad leaders and bring them here.
Okay, sir!
Jesus, and here I thought that bastard was an ace.
Corporal Yoon Joon Young...
- Is this right? - No, sir.
- Well? Is it? - I'm sorry, sir.
Time to get up!
Rise and shine!
Hey, it was you, right?
Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
I apologize.
Hey, Min Seok, get your mentee under control.
Hey, Im Da Hye.
Sort out your new recruit.
Sorry, sir.
For God's sake.
I'm sorry.
Take care.
Even though you're a private,
I thought you'd be different than the others.
Seriously, I trusted you, what the hell?
- I'm sorry. - I told you to wake me
if something was confusing or seemed off!
Wait, you didn't doze off, did you?
No, it really wasn't that...
I mistook the time...
And here I was praising you, what a mess.
I'm gonna smoke this like a boss!
Good morning.
Park Min Seok, giving a lecture?
[Smoking Area] It's not the private's fault, is it?
The teacher's in the wrong.
No...
Corporal Park taught me well. It was my mistake.
Oh, covering for your senior, too?
Park Min Seok, you're really something, huh?
Handing down your screw-ups, too?
No, really, it wasn't his fault.
I got the time wrong.
Oh, Ace Kim Hyeon Uk!
Damn it, you should've been with me instead of Min Seok.
Hey, seriously, do better next time.
Yes, I will!
Finally acting like a senior soldier!
Why are you guys like this?
Got it?
- Yes, sir. - Ten minutes until roll call!
- Let's go. - Okay, let's head in.
Looking at this bastard act, I can't believe I'm getting discharged.
Do better next time, I'm serious.
I will, sir.
Okay.
Yes, firstly...
Have the operations officers run the meeting.
Yes, I'll get the report when I get there.
Yes.
Right, take care, then.
Lieutenant Colonel Byeon!
Fancy seeing you here!
Chungseong.
It's been a while.
Yes, it's good to see you again.
I'm so tired!
Did your shift go well?
Of course it did, punk.
Hey, Bit Na Ri, what's for breakfast today?
Today's stir-fried sausage and vegetables, and poop soup!
Poop soup, again?
- Snag the chocolate milk! - I will.
Corporal Sung Yoon Mo. Reporting for duty at barracks one!
- Can I enter? - Come in.
- What is it? - Right, so...
Effective today, you're on mess hall duty for Second Company.
What the hell is he saying?
"Mess hall duty?"
Yes, that's correct.
It's so tedious, though.
Da Hye, you go.
Min Seok.
Moon Bit Na Ri.
Hyeon Uk, oh?
The privates went off earlier to do a survey, remember?
Right...
"Right?"
What, it's already too tedious for you?
Private First Class, Moon Bit Na Ri. No, sir!
This bastard's slacking so much.
Who's going to teach him?
The teacher...
Damn, this shit reeks!
Go scrub the food bins.
Why the hell do they need an officer for this?
I really don't get it.
Are you even trying? Use your muscles!
I'm sorry!
It's so damn heavy, there's so much food waste.
The menu was trash, right?
I liked it!
What was nice about it?
Sausages with vegetables, beef bulgogi, squid and radish soup!
Seaweed soup, stir-fried potatoes, seaweed snacks.
And honestly, they should always do the tteok dumpling soup!
Is there anything you don't find delicious?
Nothing so far!
If there's nothing so far, there won't be anything!
Hey, stop, stop!
If everyone were like Bit Na Ri, cooking would be worth it.
But honestly, I like everything you guys make!
Really? Then why don't you become a cook?
I mean, the food storehouse is packed, and you can eat all the sausages you want.
Wait... really?
- Of course! - Hey, leave the kid alone.
Don't let him fool you, he's an elite.
So people with high credentials can't be mess hall cooks?
I graduated college, too!
Damn, I feel alienated suddenly.
Squad, attention!
Salute to the Mess Hall Tiger!
Chungseong! Love...
Why are you joking around, Staff Sergeant Choi?
Hey, he outranks you, idiot, it's only right for you to salute him!
- Damn right. - I'm not a cat though!
Is the old man coming?
What old man?
The waste removal man.
You know that, right?
That there are only two vehicles that get a free pass through our main gate?
Wait, is that true?
The waste removal man's truck.
- And the vending machine lady. - Goodness, it's boiling.
Open sesame!
Nice.
Chungseong! Love you!
My goodness!
You're back from leave?
Yes, ma'am!
What did you get up to?
I broke up with my girlfriend.
Hey, why the long face? You'll see her again!
- Thank you. - Of course.
Have a good day!
Wow, that's so interesting!
Wait, but where does the food waste go?
This? A pig farm, I reckon?
From what I've heard, the old man doesn't actually own a farm.
Wait, then what does he do with all this slop?
Well, it's just something I heard.
I'm not certain.
I think that's him there!
Okay, he's coming. Stop, stop.
Chungseong! Love you!
Good job!
Why are you so late, sir?
Damn, my hip!
I had some business to do. I was a bit busy!
You got a problem?
No, but, I feel like your mustache gets longer every time we meet!
Damn, this punk!
You got promoted to sergeant, now you're running your mouth, huh?
"Sir!"
"Please, can I have a cigarette?"
Feels like just yesterday.
You've gotten pretty cocky, Choi Il Gu!
Me? Since when?
Wait, who's this? A new recruit?
Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri!
- You're "Private First Class?" - Yes, that's right!
You bastard, it took you getting to that rank to finally report to me, huh?
I'm sorry!
Attention!
At ease.
- Moon Bit Na Ri. - Private First Class Moon Bit Na Ri!
Where's all your spark, huh?
It's...
Okay, enough.
I don't know how well you can do in the military, but do well.
If you have any problems, call me!
Not that I'll be much help, but...
Yes, okay, sir!
Wow, this is heavy.
I said, it's heavy.
Right, yeah, I'll help!
One, two...
- Choi Il Gu. - Yes?
What are you doing?
I was getting to it. Why are you rushing me?
Look at this guy.
It's totally covered in slop.
- A little help! - Yes, sir!
One, two, three!
Wow, I remember when Choi was clueless.
Now look at him, he should be running the unit!
Well done, boys!
- Yes, head in. - Yes, yes.
But...
no salute?
Right... Chungseong! Love you!
Chungseong! Love you!
By the way, last time the pork was a bit salty.
Keep that in mind!
Yes, understood.
- Good work. - Yes, drive safely.
- Goodbye! - Goodbye!
- You heard him, keep it in mind! - Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Wait, don't you think that was a bit strange?
- What was? - That he said it was too salty?
Doesn't that mean he's tried it?
Wait.
From what I've heard, the old man doesn't actually own a farm.
Then what does he do with all this slop?
The pork was a bit salty, keep that in mind!
What?
No way...
The vending machine tastes different.
- That's because you're getting discharged! - Oh?
Chungseong! Love you.
This guy's acting sketch.
Hey!
Corporal Sung Yoon Mo!
What's this?
[Guard Duty] Why are we on guard duty?
Why would they put two last-years together?
Hey, you bastard.
Even the base cats could get past two final-years on guard duty.
Might as well be a revolving door!
What if we trip and twist an ankle going up the stairs, huh?
This is unbelievable, seriously.
Did the Company Commander or First Sergeant say anything about this?
Like "excuse them from watch" or something?
They didn't say anything.
They just said to put you two on duty because so many people are on leave.
Hey, No Wan Yong!
Corporal No Wan Yong.
You get it, right? Go talk to them and get our shifts covered.
Yes, I will go talk to them.
That bastard knew all along.
- Let's go. - Yeah.
Have a good day.
Take care.
You!
Raise that finger again and you're dead meat, seriously!
No, I-I didn't, really!
You thought we didn't know, huh?
I-I really didn't do that!
But... there's something behind you!
Watch your own back, bastard!
No, I mean, there's something there! I'm just telling you, it's...
I-I did clearly t-tell you.
Jesus, so embarrassing.
Hey, Sung Yoon Mo, clean this up!
Y-Yes, okay.
When will those bastards get discharged?
Command Sergeant Major. Chungseong! Love you!
Sorry, I'll clean it up right now!
Yes, sir!
Chungseong! Love you!
Okay.
Corporal No Hee Jeong.
What?
How did you understand that?
- What? - Not gonna lie,
I couldn't understand a word he said.
I see.
- Me neither. - Wait, what?
I think I misheard you.
There's no one in our unit who can fully understand what he's saying.
Then, how...
You think these years of seniority mean nothing, huh?
- Sorry? - Just listen closely, okay?
Just pick up the key words.
Look, what did he say earlier?
Euugh...
I-I'm not sure.
"Blah blah blah, fallen leaves."
Euugh... fallen leaves...
"Blah blah blah, central corridor."
Eugghhh... central corridor...
"Blah blah blah..." then what?
Eugh... with a broom!
With a broom.
I'm n-not sure.
"Broom," you dimwit, a broom!
That's how you piece it together.
What's a "broom?"
You're so...
Do you live your life without using your brain?
Just floating through life, not a single thought in your head?
Connect the dots, man, it's the thing you sweep the floor with!
Oh, that thing!
Makes sense now, huh?
The main corridor is filthy from all those leaves,
so keep a broom with you and clean up whenever you see them.
- Okay? - Got it.
- Yoon Mo. - Yes?
Yoon Mo.
- What? - Okay?
- Sorry? - Got it?
Right, got it.
Damn it.
I'm going to go sort this out, so stay here, don't move.
Yes, sir.
Don't mess up, okay?
Goodness me.
So clever.
I'm going to make a unit cafe.
What sort of cafe, sir?
Not a cafe for coffee.
An online one, Daum Cafe.
Where parents can sign up and see how our soldiers are holding up.
Battalion Commander, it's a bit tricky in terms of security...
- Second Company Commander. - Yes, sir.
Does a little risk stop you from getting things done?
No, sir.
The military has to change.
This place needs to change if it's going to grow, too.
Until now, everything's been buried,
covered up, and hidden under the guise of "security."
We're not talking about top-secret intel that could leak to enemy forces.
Parents deserve to know how their boys are faring in here, that's what I think.
Yes, that's right.
Good.
You can't just say "love you" without taking action or changing, can you?
Right, we'll distribute the set-up guides to each company.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Alright, that's all for now.
Alright, apart from that...
Second Company Commander.
Yes?
Keep one thing in mind, too.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
It was an order.
Yes, I understand.
- Chungseong! - Good job.
- Continue like that. - Yes, sir.
- Chungseong. Love you! - Yeah, love you.
- Hee Jeong, make a cafe. - Yes, sir?
W-What kind of cafe?
An online Daum Cafe.
Orders from the battalion commander.
Set it up, then contact the soldiers' parents
so they can get updates on how their sons are doing.
Wait, is that allowed, sir?
He said it's an order. A notice should've been sent through, check it.
I'll check now, sir.
- Yoon Mo. - Corporal Sung Yoon Mo.
Go to the internet cafe,
use the manual to make it, and report back.
[Guide to Set-up and Operate] Okay, I will.
[the Unit Online Cafe] Use a proper admin password this time.
None of that confusing 18-digit Pi nonsense like last time.
Yes, okay.
Something difficult to crack, but you won't forget.
Yeah, okay.
Why does my poop keep coming out like rabbit droppings?
Jeez.
What did you set as the password?
I made something difficult to crack, but I won't forget.
Okay, so what is it?
Sorry?
Show me.
Here.
[NHJIAB] What's this?
It's tricky.
I'm going to the restroom.
Wait a second.
"N", No.
"H" Hee, "J" Jeong.
"Is A Bast..."
"ion."
"Is a bastion."
You prick, come here!
You need a beating, come here!
- Get over here! - No, I...
Come here, you bastard, come on!
This prick, you, you deserve a beating!
- Oh, oh, wait! - Huh?
- Oh? - You're back, sir?
Are you harassing Yoon Mo right now?
N-No, sir.
You were though?
I was just hugging him, sir!
Was he really hugging you?
Yes, he was, sir.
- Yeah. - I don't think he was.
N-No, seriously, I was giving him a good, tight hug!
- Oh, Sergeant First Class Im. - Hi, sir.
Here you go.
As you go around, please take a good mix of photos of the guys
working and going about their day!
- Yes, sir! - Great.
Just nothing that could be classified, yeah?
- Got it, sir! - Great, good work!
Chungseong! Love you!
Yes, love you!
- Don't harass him! - No, s-seriously, I didn't!
Go to the internet cafe and change the password, now.
Yes, okay.
Now we're camera guys,
exposing the entire unit.
What a well-run military.
Platoon Sergeant, any chance you could take pictures of us too, then?
- Sure, of course. - A lone-wolf admin clerk vibe!
- Yes, yes! - Oh wow, really?
Let's pose, quickly!
Please make us look good!
Hey, of course!
- Kind of lone wolf-esque... - Yeah, yeah, cool.
Right.
Okay, taking it!
One, two...
- Three, these bastards! - Sorry, sir!
Are you joking? Take it yourself, damn.
Idiots.
I would speak out if it were wrong,
but this doesn't seem like a right-or-wrong problem.
I don't know what the right call is...
But I feel like something's going to happen.
Announcement from the admin office.
Please check today's guard duty rota.
- Once again, please check... - Hyeon Uk.
I'll go, don't worry, I'll be right back!
See you in a bit.
Thank you!
You did well!
- Corporal Park Min Seok! - Yeah?
You and Hyeon Uk are on 2 a.m. duty!
- Oh really? - Yes, sir.
Hyeon Uk, this is your first guard posting, right?
Private Kim Hyeon Uk. Yes, sir, it is!
- Come sit! - Yes, sir.
Hey, brief him well so yesterday's mess doesn't happen again.
I will, sir, but we're going together, so it should be fine.
Keep your wits about you, Min Seok.
I will, no need to worry!
Did you memorize all the passwords?
Cute.
Don't smile!
Goddammit, why does the First Sergeant keep calling me out for drinks?
As if things aren't hard enough, now I have to drink shitty booze.
Wait, Park Min Ju?
Why is she here?
So cool.
Huh?
What the hell.
Im Seong Min, damn...
What the hell?
Sergeant First Class Park Min Ju?
Sergeant First Class Park!
Chungseong!
I-It's me, it's Staff Sergeant Choi Il Gu!
"Choi Il Gu?"
I-I used to be Min Seok's squad leader and made staff sergeant recently...
Sorry.
- I... - My body tends to react first, so...
Jeez... I nearly died.
Any later and you would've.
What brings you out here though?
- I see... - It's not like that.
It's not!
I didn't say anything!
- If you have time, then... - Yes?
you want to die?
Oh my, I'm sorry.
Keep what you saw here today a secret.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Right, then.
I'll take the bill now!
Would it be okay...
if I helped you out?
Really?
Yes, really.
Lights out!
Setting.
Yes, okay.
- Byeong Ho. - Corporal Cha Byeong Ho, confirmed.
What are you doing?
Corporal Cha Byeong Ho, blackout complete.
Corporal Ji Jeong Min, remote control ready.
- Good. - Hey!
The minute you hear footsteps, kill it, seriously, okay?
Just trust me!
If you pull that crap you did last time
and cut it at the best bit, you're dead, for real.
It'll be different this time!
Whatever, turn it on.
Yes, sir.
- I can take over! - It's okay, you do it later.
[1997]
Oh, crap!
Hey, you're increasing it!
Sorry!
Yeah, 3 is good, do 3!
[Reply 1997] Okay!
Hey, hey, it's on!
Isn't the husband getting revealed today?
You're right!
- Hyeon Uk. - Private Kim Hyeon Uk!
I'll let you watch the rerun this weekend.
- Okay, sir! - Damn, what's gonna happen?
Who the hell is that?
If I could smoke right now, this would be perfect.
Man, ever since you got a girlfriend, you've been chain-smoking.
Guys, don't get a girlfriend.
What a load of bullshit, honestly.
- Se Gye. - Private First Class Jeon Se Gye!
Do you know who the husband is?
Shall I tell you?
- Yeah! - Wait, what, you know?
I know all the actors.
I met them when they were filming that, too.
Oh, that's right!
Dealing with those pricks these days has made me forget who Jeon Sekai is!
Private First Class Jeon Sekai.
Whatever.
So, who is it?
I missed last week's episode too.
I really need to watch the finale until the very end today.
- Lalalala... - It's Yoon Jae for sure!
I think it's Yoon Jae's brother.
It could even be Bang Seong Jae.
No way, it's definitely one of the brothers!
Should I...
- really tell you? - Yes!
The...
husband is...
Hey! I'm going to watch it, so no spoilers!
This is all I've been waiting for.
This bastard always ruins the mood, I swear, damn.
What?
Hey, look at In Guk go.
Woah, so exciting!
What will we watch once this is over?
The husband's being revealed soon!
Guys, lie down, lie down!
[Barracks No.3]
Everyone's fast asleep.
Good.
Ji Jeong Min, nice!
Corporal Ji Jeong Min!
Thank you!
How did you know it was the company commander?
Are you stepping up as the ace now?
These damn amateurs!
It's all in the footsteps!
The night watch guards scamper around quickly.
But the officers are like "boom, boom, boom!"
Like they're scoping as they walk!
Now that's seniority...
Was that just my imagination?
I swear you guys were awake.
Looks like you're all asleep, though?
That's so strange.
The top feels all warm, like a TV that's just been turned off.
It's weird, right, Jeong Min?
C-Corporal Ji Jeong Min!
Sorry, sir.
Were you watching "Reply 1997?"
Yes, I was.
Okay, I like that one too, so I understand!
Thank you, sir!
- Don't watch it! - Yes, sir.
Stop watching, starting now!
- Yes, sir! - Seriously, don't!
I won't, sir!
- Goodnight! - Yeah.
Man, it never goes right.
I'm so sorry.
- Right, set it up again. - Okay, on it.
I'll do it this time!
Okay, World Jeon, you do it!
- Do it well! - Okay!
Hey, I bet 10,000 won of frozen snacks that it's Yoon Jae's brother!
I bet it's not, and I'll get snacks from PX!
- PX it is, then! - PX bread!
Hey, be quiet, guys. The volume's at 3 so it's hard to hear!
Ugh, I'm envious.
I wonder if my Su Ah's watching this too.
I want to get married, too, damn.
He's gonna come out now!
There, there!
That scared me.
I'm today's DJ, Baek Ho!
You're all probably dying to know who the husband is right now.
Everyone knows I'm not that strict,
so why are you all sneaking around?
If the squad leaders had just come and asked, I would've let you watch it!
No, don't come over now, it's lights out!
You guys didn't tell me,
but I'll tell you guys.
- Tell us what? - What?
Oh wait, no, no!
- No... - No, I don't want to know!
He's coming.
Oh?
Spit it out, man, run, run!
You say it first!
Spit it out, come on, quickly!
- No, no, no! - Quickly!
Who is it?
The husband's Yoon Yoon Jae! That's all, good night!
What!
- No way! - That's not true, right?
N-No way, no, it's not.
I'm her husband.
I can't believe it. It's a joke!
It's Yoon Jae?
- Why did he do that, seriously! - Commander Cho, why!
This fucking sucks.
- Let's sleep now. - Good night.
Seriously, man!
He's so mean, honestly!
Yoon Yoon Jae.
I really liked the company commander...
Not anymore, though.
Seriously, he's too harsh!
- Turn the TV off. - Yes, sir.
- Where are you going? - I'm going to get the gun store key.
Stop him. He's being for real.
Huh? You can't!
N-No, you can't!
He said Yoon Yoon Jae.
Give me a hug.
Private First Class Jeon Se Gye.
Cozy.
That's entertaining, too!
Oh my.
- Company Commander! - What?
Seriously!
Isn't that too cruel?
Do you know what my nickname is?
I don't, sir!
"Spoiler Mario!"
"Spoiler Mario..."
But how did you know who the husband was?
If you saw last week's episode, it's obvious!
That was fun!
For God's sake!
Dong Woo.
Corporal Kim Dong Woo!
Want some ramen?
- Yes, sir! - Great!
Now I can really... see the end.
But there's nothing you can do as a private.
It was always like that for me as a private.
I was scolded every day.
But you're doing well, so honestly there's nothing to worry about.
When you get to corporal, it's honestly so great.
They always say time's so slow to pass,
but it does eventually.
Oh, it's already time!
Have I been talking too much about myself?
No, sir!
- It was interesting! - Really?
How are you settling in?
Thanks to you, it's been easier.
Oh, really? Thanks!
What a strange coincidence, right?
Yes, that's right.
Really, when I first saw you,
I thought, "This is fate."
Right?
I really thought we'd never cross paths again
after we left training camp!
It's so strange!
Someone's coming.
It's Corporal Kim Dong Woo coming to change shifts.
- Hyeon Uk. - Private Hyeon Uk.
How was it, manageable?
- Yes, sir. - Wow.
Once you've done it a few times, you'll be sick of it!
Did Park Min Seok just blabber on about himself?
No, sir!
Oh, well, I kind of did.
But still, only about fun stuff!
Really, like what?
About all the ups and downs in my life.
And, well,
talking about girls who confessed to me, stuff like that.
You sure those weren't rejections?
I've never been rejected before!
- Really? - Yeah, I'm super popular!
The short hair helps!
I was no joke when my hair was long.
Always keep your finger off the trigger.
Understood, sir.
Hyeon Uk, you tried it at training camp, right?
Yes, sir.
If you're not sure, just copy Min Seok.
Yes, understood.
- Present arms. - Presenting.
- Remove magazine. - Removing.
Corporal Park Min Seok, no issues.
Private Kim Hyeon Uk, no issues.
Private Kim Hyeon Uk.
- Cycle the bolt two or three times. - Cycling the bolt two or three times.
- Check the chamber. - Checking the chamber. Chamber is clear.
- Shoulder arms. - Shoulder arms.
- Selector to semi. - Selector to semi.
- Fire. - Firing.
Trigger pull, all clear.
Fire.
- What was that? - What?
Was that a gunshot?
Assistant Platoon Leader! We have a problem!
- What happened? - Well... outside...
Speak up, you punk. What happened?
I was checking the gun, then...